Nicholas Forgrave

(517)755-8251, forgravenick@gmail.com

Professional Objective

Punctual, organized, and highly motivated with two years of retail experience that has built a solid base of interpersonal communication skills, helping to move towards attaining a bachelor's degree in journalism. I am looking to further my practical experience in visual design and communication.

Qualifying Skills

- •Experience using Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator
- Computer Navigation
- •Microsoft Office:

Word, Excel, Outlook,

PowerPoint

- Document Management
- Attention to Detail
- Professional Emailing

- Calling Clients
- Client Relations
- Trustworthy
- Team Player
- Personable
- •Reliable
- •Fast Learner

Educational Experience

Michigan State University,

2017 - Present

Courses: International News and Government, Writing and Reporting News, Visualizing Data and Info Graphics, Contemporary Communities.

Lansing Community College,

Fall 2016 - Summer 2017

Courses: Ethics in Media, American Cultural Experience, Finite Math with College Algebra, Writing about Literature and Ideas.

Ferris State University,

Fall 2015 - Spring 2016

Courses: Intro. To Sociology, Intro. To Micro-Systems Software, Environmental Biology, Intro. To U.S. Legal Systems.

Work Experience

Michigan State Federal Credit Union Financial Service Representative July 2018-Present

- Working to assist members doing day to day transactions within their accounts as well as
- assessing potential opportunities to offer other products and services that the credit union has to offer to help them acheave financial security

Sam's Club, Lansing, MI Tire and Battery Technician/Wireless Sales Expert May 2016 - January 2018

- Communicating with customers and assisting them with selecting the proper tires or batteries
- Installed and documented the work done on vehicles, filing away the proper paperwork for records.
- After seven months, received a promotion to the Wireless Sales Desk
- Assessed members needs in day to day needs and matching cell phones that conformed to their budget and needes per available carriers
- Maintained digital inventory of wireless merchandise as well as
- professionally communicated and networked with company systems technicians and phone carrier representatives.

Sam's Club, Lansing, MI January 2015 August 2015

- Managed the parking lot for cleanleness and organization
- Assisted members with heavy items and placing products into vehicles as requested at checkout